Okay, this is it.
You sure you wanna do this?
HeIIo, Mrs. Ross.
WeII, heIIo, Mr. RacheI.
-Whoa!
-Oh, my God!
Come on, Pheebs, hurry!
Okay! Okay!
Oh, my God!
Is everybody getting married?
No running in the chapeI.
Hey, don't you give me
any of your-- Hey!
Why are you here?
Ross and RacheI Ieft a message.
They're getting married.
-Isn't that why you guys are here?
-Yes. Why eIse wouId we be here?
What happened?
Did we miss it?
We missed it.
Maybe you wouIdn't have
if you couId run in the chapeI!
I can't beIieve they got married.
I know! I didn't even know
they were dating.
I don't think they're as much dating
as they are...
...two bottIes of vodka waIking
around in human form.
This is insane.
What's the big deaI?
It's not Iike it's a reaI marriage.
What?
If you marry in Vegas,
you're onIy married in Vegas.
If you marry here,
you're married everywhere.
ReaIIy?
Yeah.
Oh, my God!
Oh, weII.
The One After Vegas
Why are we in bed together?
I don't know.
-Did we--?
-I don't know.
Do you have any cIothes on?
Yes.
-ReaIIy?
-No.
But we didn't have...
...sex, did we?
I don't remember much
about Iast night.
It was such a bIur.
I remember Iaughing.
I Iaughed a Iot.
Then we didn't have sex.
WeII, so, what did we do Iast night?
I don't know, but I think
it was a Iot of fun.
LuckiIy, not too much fun, right?
-I don't think so.
-Oh, thank God.
Oh, I mean,
we were reaIIy drunk.
I'm gIad we didn't
do anything stupid.
TeII me about it.
Morning, Pheebs.
WeII, my movie has been
officiaIIy canceIed.
Joey, I'm so sorry.
You want my breakfast?
Too depressed to eat.
I'II probabIy eat in, Iike,
five minutes.
I'II fIy home with you.
What time is your fIight?
-What about my cab?
-I don't need that anymore.
You borrowed my cab.
You have to drive it back.
I don't wanna drive back
by myseIf. I get IoneIy.
How about if you come with me?
-It's a Iong trip.
-That wouId be great.
We couId taIk and pIay games.
This couId be our chance
to, Iike, renew our friendship.
Are you asking me
to have a ''frienaissance''?
Sure?
AII right. AIthough, I don't think we
need one. I never stopped Ioving you.
So has anybody taIked
to Dr. and Mrs. GeIIer yet?
They Ieft me a message.
They'II be here.
Where is the waitress? I'm starving.
It's a buffet, man.
Here's where I win
aII my money back!
I gotta taIk to you.
Sure.
What's up?
Monica and I aImost got married.
My God!
That's huge!
Wait a minute. Why wasn't I invited?
And who was gonna be your best man?
Don't say Ross. Do not say Ross.
I just don't think that Monica and I
are ready yet. I Iove her...
...but seeing Ross and RacheI
come out of that chapeI...
...was Iike a wake-up caII that Monica
and I are moving so fast, you know.
How do I teII her
without crushing her?
TeII her she's not marriage materiaI.
What?
GirIs say it to me aII the time.
And if she's anything Iike me,
she's just gonna be reIieved.
How do I teII him that it's too soon?
He's gonna think
I don't Iove him anymore.
-WeII, you don't.
-Yes, I do.
Good. I was just testing you.
-Hey.
-Oh, hi.
We were just taIking about bacon.
No, we were taIking about tennis.
Tennis is more beIievabIe.
Thank you.
Coffee.
What?
Are we gonna taIk about
what you guys did Iast night?
What do you mean ''Iast night''?
Nothing happened Iast night.
Ross invited us aII to watch.
What is the matter with you?
We weren't gonna miss
our friends getting married.
Who got married?
You did.
What?
-HeIIo. We didn't get married.
-No, we didn't. That's ridi--
Wait, wait, wait.
I remember being in a chapeI.
They wouId not Iet us get married
when we were that drunk.
They Iet you get married.
Most peopIe who marry
in Vegas are drunk.
Now, I'm drunk right now.
I can't have a mimosa with breakfast?
I'm on vacation.
What are you gonna do?
WeII, I guess we find
a divorce Iawyer.
WeII, I think-- I think
Ross aIready has one.
Yeah, that guy's finaIIy gonna
be abIe to put in that pooI.
Okay.
Now, this one's free, right?
Because you paid for the first two.
Laugh it up, but the joke's on you...
...because we don't need
to get divorced.
-We're just gonna get an annuIment.
-An annuIment?
Ross, I don't think surgery
is the answer here.
Oh, that's your thing!
What?
Your thing. You're the guy
who gets divorced.
No, no, that's not ''my thing.''
I do not Iove getting divorced.
Yes, you do. This is
your third divorce.
You Iove divorce so much,
you're probabIy gonna marry it...
...and then it won't work out,
so you're gonna have to divorce it.
I'm so drunk.
-You wanna pIay some Pai Gow?
-Maybe.
But I kind of think we shouId taIk
about Iast night.
That's a good idea.
I wanna taIk about Iast night too...
-...and I don't know what Pai Gow is.
-I see.
-So what shouId we do?
-I don't know.
I know I Iove you.
Where are we on the whoIe
''going back...
...to where they have the marriages''
thing? I Iove you.
That's a good question.
Last night we Iet the dice decide.
We shouId Ieave it
up to fate again. I Iove you!
We don't get married
unIess there's a sign.
So say...
...you roII another eight,
then there's a sign...
...that we shouId marry.
Eight we get married...
...but 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 9, 1 0,
1 1 , 1 2, we don't get married.
Sounds great.
Hey, we got a shooter.
Money, pIease.
-Ready?
-Ready.
Come on, eight.
Yes, yes, eight.
Eight, easy eight.
-I can't beIieve I roIIed an eight.
-That was so unIikeIy.
Let's get married.
I guess.
Last night I roIIed a hard eight.
It was the wrong kind of eight.
No wedding! Damn it!
I wanted it so bad!
Wanna go pack?
We're doing the right thing.
Of course we are.
We Ieft it up to fate.
If we were supposed to get married,
there wouId be a sign.
Okay, you have 1 9 questions Ieft.
Use them wiseIy.
Come on, Joey. You can't win
if you don't ask any questions!
-What?
-You promised me a fun road trip.
We've been on the road for 6 hours,
and you've been asIeep for 5 and a haIf.
We are switching, and
you are going to drive back.
That wiII be your punishment,
you greedy sIeeper!
AII right.
And untiI then, you are going
to sing to me...
...because the radio's broken and you are
seIfish, but you have a nice voice.
-ReaIIy?
-Sing!
I wanna rock 'n' roll all night
Man, this is a long drive.
Are my eyes open?
No!
Morning.
-Hey.
-Hey, hubby.
ActuaIIy, I wanted to taIk to you
about that whoIe annuIment thing.
Yeah, I'm not gonna do that.
Okay.
So we'II just stay married.
Yes, exactIy.
And I wiII make everyone
caII me Mrs. GeIIer.
Wow, this is so amazing.
I reaIIy thought I'd have to
taIk you into this more.
Now I'm scared because I don't
actuaIIy think you're kidding.
I'm not kidding.
Look...
...I can't have three
faiIed marriages.
I can't, okay?
I am not gonna be that guy.
Okay? No, no. That is not gonna be
''my thing.''
So, what, we just
stay married forever?
I don't know.
I mean, I haven't worked it aII
out yet, but....
Okay, I know it's a bit crazy--
How is this going
to affect you, reaIIy?
I mean, you fiII some form out
once in a whiIe...
...instead of checking the box ''Miss,''
you check the box that says, ''Mrs.''
It's right next to it.
Okay. I'm sorry, you're right.
You know what?
We can stay married...
...because I thought that the boxes
were far away from each other.
-No, they're right--
-Ross!
AII right.
Just...
...pIease take a moment here...
...and think about what
you're asking of me. Okay?
I am asking you to do me a favor.
You are asking me to be your wife.
And as my wife, I think
you shouId grant me this favor.
We did make vows.
That kid kicked me reaIIy hard.
WeII, you did puII his hair.
-He took my snack.
-I'm not getting into this again.
AII right, you know what?
Hurts reaIIy bad.
WeII, I toId you not to waIk. Here.
There. There. Okay.
-This doesn't mean anything, does it?
-No.
How couId you pick up a hitchhiker?
He couId be a rap-- He couId be
a rapist or a kiIIer or something.
Don't you think I asked him that
before he got in?
I'm not taIking to you.
You go back to sIeep.
-And, you, are you a rapist?
-No.
Do you Iike car games?
Yeah, you know
the Iicense pIate game?
I Iove the Iicense pIate game!
I'II pIay. I'II pIay.
No, you need your sIeep.
Night-night.
Listen. I know you wanted
to taIk to me...
...but I have an idea that may
make you wanna stay married.
We register...
...and you get to keep
aII the presents.
No, Ross, come on. No, Iisten.
I've thought about
how to teII you this.
I came up with an anaIogy
about a IittIe goIdfish...
...in a pond that freezes over
in the winter...
...but I reaIized that was a story about
what to do when peopIe pick on you.
So I'm gonna actuaIIy save that
for my chiIdren's book.
-What's up?
-Oh, sorry.
The bottom Iine, Ross...
...is we cannot stay married.
-I don't know if that's true--
-Oh, but it is.
Okay. You know what this is?
This is a difference of opinion.
-When that happens in a marriage--
-Ross, come on!
This is not a marriage!
This is the worId's worst hangover!
Ross, Iisten, if you do not
get this annuIment, I wiII.
AII right.
AII right, I'II do it.
Thank you.
Hey, hey...
...is there any such thing
as an annuIment shower?
There's the train station.
This is where I get off.
I have your address
and phone number.
I have your name and the fact
that you're a drifter.
So baII's pretty much
in your court.
AII right. See you, Pheebs.
Come on, Pheebs, I can't
take this anymore.
PIease taIk to me.
Let me make it up to you.
Ground control to Major Tom
Commencing countdown
Engines on
Take your protein pills
And put your helmet on
-This is--
-Stop it! Stop it! No!
That's not fair. You know I can't
resist that beautifuI voice.
Pheebs, Iook, I am so sorry.
I promised you a fun
road trip with your friend...
...and I didn't deIiver, okay?
Now I know that you think being awake
is an important part of friendship.
So I wiII strive to stay awake
for as Iong as I know you.
You can stiII sIeep
at night and stuff.
Thank you.
So can we pIay 20 Questions now?
I got a good one.
I thought about it since Kansas.
Okay.
Is it...
...a kind of hot sandwich?
Yes.
Is it a meatbaII sub?
That is incredibIe!
You are the master!
Bug!
-Enough aIready!
-WeII, you didn't have to catch them!
-You Iook Iike you're--
-Don't say it!
Don't even think it.
AII right.
ChandIer, enjoy your handfuI.
ShouId we just get married?
AII the signs are teIIing us to do it.
I'm sick of the signs.
-I'm happy the way things are.
-Me too.
-I don't want change, do you?
-No.
Then nothing changes!
Everything stays the same!
Go unpack. It's been three days,
and it drives me insane!
Jeez, reIax, it's not
Iike we're mar--
You know, I was thinking,
what if I...
...unpack here?
AII your stuff wouId be here.
WeII...
...what if aII my stuff was here?
Then you'd be going back
and forth aII the time.
Doesn't make any sense.
Okay.
What if we Iive together,
and you get what I'm saying?
Live together?
There've been no signs for that.
Me asking is kind of a sign.
Yes! Yes! Yes!
Okay. Okay, wait.
Wait, wait, wait.
Here's your key. Here's your key.
Now go out and christen it!
Go out and come back in!
Door hasn't been Iocked
in five years, but okay.
-Ready?
-Ready!
The key broke in the Iock,
and I can't get in.
Wait. Oh, my God, I can't get out!
-This isn't a sign!
-No, it's a very oId key!
-It's an oId key!
-Oh, my God, it's oId!
I Iove you.
Are you hugging the door right now?
No.
Yeah, yeah, me neither.
So did everything go aII right
with the annuIment?
Oh, yeah. No probIems.
It's aII taken care of.
Ross, thank you.
Do you wanna go see a movie?
-Yeah, why not?
-Pheebs?
No, thanks.
I've aIready seen one.
Okay, I'm gonna get my sweater.
You wanna hear something weird?
AIways.
I didn't get the annuIment.
What?
We're stiII married.
Don't teII RacheI. See you Iater.
What are you doing?
Key is stuck in the Iock.
I can fix it. HoId on.
Watch out, watch out.
It stiII doesn't work.
I'm not finished.
Nice job, Joe.
You're quite the craftsman!