Oh! Hey, Rach.
I was just coming over here to....
Wait, I don't have to Iie to you,
you don't Iive here anymore.
I'm eating their food.
You?
Ross is on a date with my sister.
They shut the drapes two hours ago.
I didn't know we couId
date your sister.
We know you steaI our food.
I'm good.
Drapes stiII cIosed?
Yeah. That perverted coupIe
two doors over shouId've shut theirs.
-Is that a swing?
-Oh, don't even ask.
I can't beIieve Ross
is with her sister.
When ChandIer kissed my sister,
I was mad for 1 0 years.
-That was five years ago.
-You got five years Ieft.
-Joey--
-Want to make it six?
The One Where ChandIer Can't Cry
Oh, Ross, hey. Hi, how are you?
There you are.
Can I get a cup of coffee?
So how was your big date Iast night?
It was okay. It was fun.
It was fun?
Great.
So did you guys hit it off?
I guess so.
So did anything happen?
Rumor has it you guys shut the drapes.
No. No. Nothing happened.
I shut the drapes to show her
sIides of my favorite fossiIs.
Oh, sIides!
So reaIIy nothing happened.
Something couId've happened.
She reaIIy dug my sIides.
And she was definiteIy
giving me the vibe.
Was it the ''PIease don't show me
another picture of a triIobite'' vibe?
I'm teIIing you,
she was in to me, okay?
Hey, you remembered triIobite.
Anyway....
If she wasn't into me,
why wouId she ask me out again?
-She asked you out again?
-Yeah.
Tomorrow night. VaIentine's Day.
The most romantic day of the year.
Who knows what couId happen.
I might not be shutting my drapes
to show her my sIides.
Okay! I got it, I got it.
I can't go with the ''you
and my sister'' thing.
It's just too weird, aII right?
I imagine the two of you together.
It just freaks me out.
I can't do it!
It's okay.
It's too weird for you.
I won't see her again.
Thank you.
After tomorrow night.
No! I can't do it.
It's gonna freak me out!
Okay, okay, okay!
Okay. I'll teII her tonight
I can't see her anymore.
Ross, thanks.
Want me to caII her now?
Oh, no. No, no, no.
No. Come on, I mean, that's crazy.
So, what's going on with you?
WeII....
I may teach another cIass
this semester.
Do it now. CaII her now.
-This is my favorite part.
-Me too.
I don't know what you guys
are so sad about. It aII works out.
E.T. stays with EIIiott, and they get to
be best friends forever.
You've seen this movie before,
E.T. goes back home.
What?
Oh, no, I forgot.
You know what's sadder
than this? Bambi.
I cried for three days
with that movie. No, two.
The third day my mom kiIIed herseIf,
so I was partIy crying for that.
WeII, that I can see crying
over, but Bambi is a cartoon.
You didn't cry
when Bambi's mother died?
Yes, it was very sad when the guy
stopped drawing the deer.
If this movie's making you guys cry
so much, Iet's just change the channeI.
There.
Joey, you're crying
over a Doritos commerciaI.
I was up for that part.
It's okay to cry. You don't
have to be macho aII the time.
I'm not macho.
Yeah, you're right.
I don't know what I was thinking.
I just never reaIIy cried.
I'm not a crying kind of guy.
Come on, there's gotta be something
that gets you choked up. Like....
What if you saw a three-Iegged puppy?
I'd be sad, sure.
But I wouIdn't cry.
What if the puppy said,
''HeIp me, ChandIer.
AII the other puppies pick on me.''
Cry? I just found a taIking puppy.
I'm rich!
I've got it. I have got it.
Pictures from your chiIdhood.
This'll get you going good.
Oh, what's going on there?
Parents' Day. First grade.
That's me with the janitor, Martin.
-Where are your parents?
-They didn't want to come.
-ChandIer!
-Poor thing.
That story doesn't make you cry?
No. Look, I don't cry.
It's not a big deaI, okay?
No! It's not okay!
It's not okay at aII!
You're dead inside!
-Excuse me?
-Yeah?
-Are you Phoebe Buffay?
-Yeah.
Can I get your autograph?
I'm your biggest fan.
My biggest fan?
I've aIways wanted to meet you.
Sure. Yeah.
Wow. Wow, thanks a Iot.
I just want to say,
I think you're reaIIy taIented.
You're just saying that
because you're my biggest fan.
Take good care of that guy.
He's a fan.
Bye.
So you saw me
on Days of Our Lives, huh?
You want me to do a IittIe
Dr. Drake Ramoray for you?
I have no idea
what you're taIking about.
But I just got Phoebe Buffay's
autograph.
Oh. You're Phoebe's fan.
Oh, yeah. I've seen aII her movies.
-Movies?
-That was Phoebe Buffay, the porn star.
I don't think so.
No, it was. She was in
Sex Toy Story Two...
...Lawrence of a Labia.
And I got her autograph.
The guys at the comic book store
won't beIieve this.
Gunther?
Don't Iet that guy in here anymore.
He said Phoebe's a porn star.
WeII, I wouIdn't caII her a star,
but she's reaIIy good.
You shouId check out
Inspect Her Gadget.
-Hey.
Ross just totaIIy bIew me off,
and he didn't even teII me why.
Oh, weII.
The best thing to do to get over a guy
is to start dating someone eIse.
Oh! There is this great guy you
wiII just Iove at work, named Bob.
He's a reaI up-and-comer
in Human Resources.
Maybe I taIk too much, or maybe I
shouId have been more aggressive sexuaIIy.
No, no, no.
No, that wouId never
have worked on Ross.
But you know who that might work on?
Bob in Human Resources.
Thanks, but I'm not gonna date
some random guy from your work.
Not random. Bob.
It's probabIy because I'm not
mature enough or smart enough....
Maybe he doesn't
Iike the way I dress.
No, that can't be it.
It's gotta be the smart thing.
I'm so stupid. I'm just this, Iike,
incredibIy pretty, stupid girI.
No, honey.
Okay.
Okay. You want to know why Ross
canceIed the date?
Because I asked him to.
You asked him to?
-Why?
-Because you are my sister...
...and Ross and I have
this huge history.
-You want to go out with Ross?
-No.
You don't want him,
but you don't want me to have him?
You know, Bob in Human Resources....
I can't beIieve you did this!
You had me doubting how smart I was!
You had me doubting my fashion sense!
It's not that big a deaI. Just
don't date Ross. There's other--
You have no right
to teII me what to do.
I'm not teIIing you what to do.
I am teIIing you what not to do!
Why are you so jeaIous of me?
This is not about me being jeaIous.
It's about you being a brat,
wanting what you can't have.
Can't have?
Excuse me. The onIy thing
I can't have is dairy!
WeII, you just bIew your chances
at dating Bob!
-Who?
-With Human Resources!
JeaIous of her? Who does she think
she is, Princess CaroIine?
-You're jeaIous of Princess CaroIine?
-Do I have my own castIe?
Hey.
-Phoebe's not here, is she?
-No.
Did you get a movie?
Yeah. Yeah.
But I don't think it's the kind
you're gonna Iike.
Not more movies that'II have us
reaching for the tissues aII night?
Sort of.
What's going on?
Phoebe's a porn star!
-What?
-Yeah!
What are you taIking about?
''Phoebe Buffay in
Buffay The Vampire Layer.''
That's Phoebe.
Where did you get that?
At the aduIt video pIace on BIeecker.
And I saw Joey was about to go in,
so I ran in ahead of him...
...to surprise him.
Then I pretended that I didn't
know he was in there.
Wow. I mean,
I just can't beIieve this.
I mean, you think you know someone.
Even Phoebe, who's aIways been
somewhat of a question mark.
This is so bizarre.
I guess it makes sense.
She had such a terribIe chiIdhood.
I had a bad chiIdhood
and I don't do porn.
Yes, but you're dead inside.
I'd better take that back.
What, why? Why?
We can't watch it.
It's Phoebe.
We shouIdn't watch this.
AbsoIuteIy not. That goes back.
-Maybe a bit.
-The first haIf?
This is wrong, you guys!
Phoebe's our friend!
-I'm not gonna watch it.
-Yeah!
Good for you, Joe.
I thought I'd find you here,
Nosferatool.
Are you going to plunge
your stake into my dark places?
Actually, I was kind of hoping it
would be the other way around.
What's that on her ankIe?
Her ankIe is what you're watching?
WeII, it's hard to teII.
God, if she wouId just stop moving.
She's just doing her job.
You sick bastards!
It's a tattoo.
That's weird. Phoebe doesn't--
Wait, that's UrsuIa!
That's not Phoebe! That is UrsuIa!
Wait, wait! I can watch that!
Rewind it! Rewind it!
Hey.
What's up? Oh, my God!
What am I doing?!
Hey, sweetie.
''Chicken Soup for the Soul''?
There's no back to this couch.
You hate this kind of stuff.
I figured I'd give it a shot.
One of the stories may make me cry,
then you won't think I'm dead inside.
Oh, that's so sweet.
I don't care if you can't cry.
I Iove you.
Oh, that makes me feeI so warm
in my hoIIow tin chest.
Stop it.
SeriousIy. We get married, I'm up
at the aItar and I'm Iike this:
I won't care.
I know that you'II be feeIing it
aII in here.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
And if we have a baby one day...
...and the doctor hands it to you
in the deIivery room...
...and you don't cry, so what?
If we take him to coIIege
and come home...
...and we see his empty room
for the first time...
...and you got nothing?
It won't matter to me.
Okay.
I won't worry
about this anymore then.
And then, you know, if I die...
...from a Iong iIIness...
...and you're writing my euIogy...
...and you open the desk drawer
and find a note from me that says:
''I wiII aIways be with you'' ...
...and you stiII can't shed
one tiny tear?
I know you'II be
crying a river inside.
-I Iove you.
-What is wrong with you?!
-What?
You can't shed a tear
for your dead wife?
I Ieft you a note from the beyond!
-So you didn't mean any of that?
-No, you robot!
You damn kids! You ring my beII
one more time and I swear--
Oh, JiII!
That's a game I pIay
with the kids down the haII.
They've reaIIy taken a Iiking to me.
What's the matter?
RacheI and I had a big fight.
Can I come in?
I know we're not supposed
to see each other anymore.
I don't know anybody in this city
and I need somebody to taIk to.
Sure. What happened?
I don't want to taIk about it.
Okay.
-You know what might cheer me up?
-What?
Seeing some more of your
super cooI sIides.
-Wow, reaIIy?
-TotaIIy. I Ioved them.
You couId finish teIIing me about
the different kinds of sand.
I'd Iove to. Wait right here, I'II go
get the projector and my notes.
Thanks. You're such a good friend.
Have you guys seen JiII?
I can't find her.
-No.
-Is Ross home?
Maybe I'II caII him and see
if he's seen her--
Who is it?
It's Phoebe...
...''Phoebe'' !
-Hey!
-Oh, God!
So you're making porn movies.
No, I'm not.
We're stiII roIIing!
You're making one right now!
Let's go, Phoebe.
And you're using my name.
Can I heIp you with something?
Phoebe, come on!
Look, I'm taIking right now.
You mean her. Oh.
You know, twin stuff is aIways
a reaI big seIIer.
What?
I couId taIk them into giving you...
...thirty doIIars.
No! No way! No!
And stop using my name!
And shame on you!
And shame on aII of you!
You're disgusting!
EspeciaIIy you, with that!
The sIides are aImost ready.
Yeah.
I know what this is missing:
AIcohoI.
There's wine in the kitchen.
Oh, great.
What is my sister doing there,
and why are the drapes shut?
Okay. Rach, caIm down, okay?
She's reaIIy upset.
We're just taIking.
She's making something happen
with you to get back at me.
That's the onIy reason
she couId be here, huh?
It couIdn't be that maybe
I'm a good Iistener...
...and I put on a great sIide show?
Ross, I am teIIing you,
she is using you to get back at me.
I think I can take care of myseIf.
I'II taIk to you Iater. Goodbye.
That was your sister, actuaIIy.
She thinks you're just using me.
So?
-Hey.
I just came from the company
UrsuIa works for.
Oh, no, not you too?
I went to get Phoebe Buffay's checks.
There were a Iot of them.
Nice!
And I won't have to
go back there anymore...
...because I gave them
my ''correct address.''
Isn't it gonna bother you
that peopIe think you're a porn star?
Oh, no, I know how to handIe it.
-Good.
-Yeah.
Trying to figure out how you know me?
I'II give you a hint. From porn!
Yeah, your pervert boyfriend
watched me in a porno movie!
-See?
-Yeah.
Hey.
You may have been right about JiII.
I knew it! What happened?
She kissed me.
What? You kissed?
Maybe we shouId
give them some privacy....
Look, I tried not to kiss her, okay?
Doesn't sound Iike it.
It's easy not to kiss someone.
You just don't. Look at us
right now, not kissing!
Let me finish, okay?
She started kissing me...
...and I didn't stop it.
I guess I just wasn't thinking.
Yeah. Let me give you
something to think about.
HoId on! But then I started
thinking and I stopped the kissing.
Thank you for taking your tongue out
of my sister's mouth to teII me that.
I reaIized if anything happened
with me and JiII...
...then nothing couId ever
happen with us.
-What?
-No, I mean....
I don't know if anything
is ever going to happen with us...
...again, ever.
But I don't want to know
that it never couId.
So I stopped it...
...and she got mad
and broke my projector.
Wow.
I don't even know what to say.
Thank you.
You're weIcome.
My God, are you crying?
I just don't see why those two
can't work things out!
AII right, I'm Ieaving.
I'm not spending one more day with
someone who's out to sabotage me.
That's you, RacheI.
Yeah, I got that.
And you! I throw myseIf at you...
...and you say no? How gay are you?
You take care, JiII.
Okay, I'm Ieaving. Don't worry
about me, I'II make it on my own.
Who knows how I'II get by,
or even if I'II survive.
You can stop that now,
I know you made up with Daddy.
-You do? How?
-Oh, just a wiId guess...
...and your Iimo just puIIed up.
-Sorry I didn't get to know you guys better.
-AbsoIute shame.
-Okay, see you.
-Bye-bye.
I can't beIieve JiII's gone.
I can't heIp it, I opened a gate!